Guide to the Vassar College Photograph Files, approximately 1865-2014
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Views. Horse car, trolley, bus, etc. [See also: V. C. Class Trees] (Folder 17.33)
- V. C. Views. Outdoor Theatre (Folder 17.34)
- V. C. Views. Quadrangle (Folder 17.35)
- V. C. Views. Raymond Avenue (Folder 17.36)
- V. C. Views. Rock Lot (OV1.198)
- V. C. Views. Shakespeare Garden (Folder 17.37)
- V. C. Views. Sunset Hill (Folder 17.38)
- V. C. Views. Sunset Lake (previously Pratt Lake) (Folder 17.39)
- V. C. Views. Sunset Lake (OV1.199)
- V. C. Views. Sunset Lake (OV3.064)
- V. C. Views. Trees [See also V. C. Class Trees] (Folder 17.40)
- V. C. Views. Trees (OV1.200-OV1.201)
- V. C. Views. Vassar Lake (Folders 18.1-18.4)
- V. C. Views. Vassar Lake (OV1.202)
- V. C. Views. Vassar Lake (OV2.116)
- V. C. Views. Winter Scenes (Folders 18.5-18.7)
- V. C. Views. Winter Scenes (OV1.203)
- V. C. War Time Activities. World War I. Miscellaneous (Folder 18.8)
- V. C. War Time Activities. World War I. Farmerettes (Folder 18.9)
- V. C. War Time Activities. World War I. Farmerettes (OV3.065)
- V. C. War Time Activities. World War I. Tank (Folder 18.10)
- V. C. War Time Activities. World War II (Folder 18.11)
- V. C. Winter Sports (Folder 18.12)
- V. C. Yale Teacher Training Program (Folder 18.13)
- Vassar, Michigan (Folder 18.14)
- Vassar in Japan (Folder 18.15)
- Washington Summer Intern Program (Folder 18.16)
- West Point (Folder 18.17)
- World Youth Congress, 1938 Aug (Folders 18.18-18.19)
- Y.W.C.A. Student Conference, Silver Bay, NY, 1912 (OV2.125)
- Yale-Vassar (Folder 18.20)
- Miscellaneous unidentified individuals, undated (Folder 18.21)
- Miscellaneous unidentified individuals, undated (OV1.206-OV1.207)
- Miscellaneous unidentified events, undated (Folder 18.22)